{
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Which is the most popular JavaScript framework?",
            "options": ["Angular", "React", "Svelte", "Vue"],
            "correctOption": 1,
            "points": 10
        },
        {
            "question": "Which company invented React?",
            "options": ["Google", "Apple", "Netflix", "Facebook"],
            "correctOption": 3,
            "points": 10
        },
        {
            "question": "What's the fundamental building block of React apps?",
            "options": ["Components", "Blocks", "Elements", "Effects"],
            "correctOption": 0,
            "points": 10
        },
        {
            "question": "What's the name of the syntax we use to describe the UI in React components?",
            "options": ["FBJ", "Babel", "JSX", "ES2015"],
            "correctOption": 2,
            "points": 10
        },
        {
            "question": "How does data flow naturally in React apps?",
            "options": [
                "From parents to children",
                "From children to parents",
                "Both ways",
                "The developers decides"
            ],
            "correctOption": 0,
            "points": 10
        },
        {
            "question": "How to pass data into a child component?",
            "options": ["State", "Props", "PropTypes", "Parameters"],
            "correctOption": 1,
            "points": 10
        },
        {
            "question": "When to use derived state?",
            "options": [
                "Whenever the state should not trigger a re-render",
                "Whenever the state can be synchronized with an effect",
                "Whenever the state should be accessible to all components",
                "Whenever the state can be computed from another state variable"
            ],
            "correctOption": 3,
            "points": 30
        },
        {
            "question": "What triggers a UI re-render in React?",
            "options": [
                "Running an effect",
                "Passing props",
                "Updating state",
                "Adding event listeners to DOM elements"
            ],
            "correctOption": 2,
            "points": 20
        },
        {
            "question": "When do we directly \"touch\" the DOM in React?",
            "options": [
                "When we need to listen to an event",
                "When we need to change the UI",
                "When we need to add styles",
                "Almost never"
            ],
            "correctOption": 3,
            "points": 20
        },
        {
            "question": "In what situation do we use a callback to update state?",
            "options": [
                "When updating the state will be slow",
                "When the updated state is very data-intensive",
                "When the state update should happen faster",
                "When the new state depends on the previous state"
            ],
            "correctOption": 3,
            "points": 30
        },
        {
            "question": "If we pass a function to useState, when will that function be called?",
            "options": [
                "On each re-render",
                "Each time we update the state",
                "Only on the initial render",
                "The first time we update the state"
            ],
            "correctOption": 2,
            "points": 30
        },
        {
            "question": "Which hook to use for an API request on the component's initial render?",
            "options": ["useState", "useEffect", "useRef", "useReducer"],
            "correctOption": 1,
            "points": 10
        },
        {
            "question": "Which variables should go into the useEffect dependency array?",
            "options": [
                "Usually none",
                "All our state variables",
                "All state and props referenced in the effect",
                "All variables needed for clean up"
            ],
            "correctOption": 2,
            "points": 30
        },
        {
            "question": "An effect will always run on the initial render.",
            "options": [
                "True",
                "It depends on the dependency array",
                "False",
                "In depends on the code in the effect"
            ],
            "correctOption": 0,
            "points": 30
        },
        {
            "question": "When will an effect run if it doesn't have a dependency array?",
            "options": [
                "Only when the component mounts",
                "Only when the component unmounts",
                "The first time the component re-renders",
                "Each time the component is re-rendered"
            ],
            "correctOption": 3,
            "points": 20
        }
    ],
    "cities": [
        {
            "cityName": "Berlin",
            "country": "Germany",
            "emoji": "üá©üá™",
            "date": "2027-02-12T09:24:11.863Z",
            "notes": "Amazing üòÉ",
            "position": {
                "lat": 52.53586782505711,
                "lng": 13.376933665713324
            },
            "id": 98443197
        },
        {
            "cityName": "Paris",
            "country": "France",
            "emoji": "üá´üá∑",
            "date": "2024-09-23T19:36:40.676Z",
            "notes": "Love",
            "position": {
                "lat": "48.84664340683584",
                "lng": "2.3469543457031254"
            },
            "id": 98443199
        },
        {
            "cityName": "Tallinn",
            "country": "Estonia",
            "emoji": "üá™üá™",
            "date": "2024-10-03T20:17:49.878Z",
            "notes": "Great!!!",
            "position": {
                "lat": "59.405957115062684",
                "lng": "24.741210937500004"
            },
            "id": 98443200
        },
        {
            "cityName": "Saint Petersburg",
            "country": "Russian Federation (the)",
            "emoji": "üá∑üá∫",
            "date": "2024-10-03T20:18:20.651Z",
            "notes": "",
            "position": {
                "lat": "59.877911874831156",
                "lng": "30.388183593750004"
            },
            "id": 98443201
        },
        {
            "cityName": "La Romana",
            "country": "Dominican Republic (the)",
            "emoji": "üá©üá¥",
            "date": "2024-10-03T20:19:10.429Z",
            "notes": "Nice Tripüòç",
            "position": {
                "lat": "18.42489620284244",
                "lng": "-68.91586303710939"
            },
            "id": 98443202
        },
        {
            "cityName": "Kaliningrad",
            "country": "Russian Federation (the)",
            "emoji": "üá∑üá∫",
            "date": "2024-10-03T20:20:47.971Z",
            "notes": "",
            "position": {
                "lat": "54.702407731003376",
                "lng": "20.5279541015625"
            },
            "id": 98443203
        }
    ]
}
